export const quizQuestions_2 = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What does JSX stand for in the context of React?',
      choices: ['JavaScript XML', 'JS Extension', 'XML Syntax', 'JS Templating'],
      correctAnswer: 'JavaScript XML',
    },
    {
      question: 'How is JSX different from HTML?',
      choices: ['There is no difference', 'JSX is a preprocessor for HTML', 'JSX allows embedding JavaScript expressions', 'HTML is used for server-side rendering'],
      correctAnswer: 'JSX allows embedding JavaScript expressions',
    },
    {
      question: 'In JSX, how do you embed JavaScript expressions?',
      choices: ['{{ expression }}', '{ expression }', '${ expression }', '(% expression %)'],
      correctAnswer: '{ expression }',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the role of Babel in JSX?',
      choices: ['It is an alternative to JSX', 'It is not related to JSX', 'It transpiles JSX into JavaScript', 'It converts JSX to HTML'],
      correctAnswer: 'It transpiles JSX into JavaScript',
    },
    {
      question: 'Can JSX elements have event handlers?',
      choices: ['No, JSX does not support events', 'Yes, only for certain elements', 'Yes, like in regular HTML', 'Only in class components'],
      correctAnswer: 'Yes, like in regular HTML',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the significance of the curly braces in JSX?',
      choices: ['To define objects', 'To denote JSX elements', 'To indicate comments', 'To enclose JavaScript expressions'],
      correctAnswer: 'To enclose JavaScript expressions',
    },
    {
      question: 'In React, can you use JSX in functional components?',
      choices: ['Yes, but only with special syntax', 'No, JSX is only for class components', 'Yes, JSX is commonly used in functional components', 'It depends on the React version'],
      correctAnswer: 'Yes, JSX is commonly used in functional components',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which method is used to render JSX content in a React component?',
      choices: ['renderJSX()', 'show()', 'displayJSX()', 'render()'],
      correctAnswer: 'render()',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of keys in a list of JSX elements?',
      choices: ['To provide styling information', 'To identify each element uniquely', 'To determine the order of elements', 'Keys are not necessary in JSX lists'],
      correctAnswer: 'To identify each element uniquely',
    },
    {
      question: 'How can you comment out sections in JSX?',
      choices: ['/* Comment */', '<!-- Comment -->', '{/* Comment */}', '// Comment'],
      correctAnswer: '{/* Comment */}',
    }
  ]
};
